kyte.tv 2009-06-08

# Kyte: Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of 12/08/2006.**

decentral.tv Corporation, a Delaware corporation ("decentral.tv"), recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually "Users") who use www.kyte.tv or other websites owned or operated by decentral.tv (the "Sites") and the related services (including, without limitation, the Kyte Flash tools, "Embeddable Flash Players", the mobile client, the WAP service or other Kyte features or applications) (collectively, the "Service") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the decentral.tv Sites and Service. decentral.tv provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the decentral.tv Sites and Service. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the decentral.tv Terms of Service. Your use of the decentral.tv Sites and Service and any personal information you provide on the decentral.tv Sites and Service remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. Please note that any graphic, picture, photo, video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the decentral.tv Sites and or the Service becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

###  The Information decentral.tv Collects 

**User Provided Information**  
You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to decentral.tv when choosing to participate in various activities on the decentral.tv Sites and the Service such as uploading graphics, pictures, images, videos, posting messages in our forums or in entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

**Cookies**  
When you visit the decentral.tv Sites or use any of the decentral.tv Service, we may send one or more "cookies" - small text files containing strings of alphanumeric characters - to your computer or device that uniquely identifies your browser. decentral.tv uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can set your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the decentral.tv Sites and Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

**Log Files**  
When you use the decentral.tv Sites and Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

###  The Way decentral.tv Uses Information 

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the decentral.tv Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide you with the features and functionality of the decentral.tv Sites and Service. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the decentral.tv Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any content (text, pictures, graphics, photos, music, videos, etc) that you submit to the decentral.tv Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major decentral.tv Site and/or Service changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the decentral.tv Sites and Service and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the decentral.tv Sites and Service; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

###  When decentral.tv Discloses Information 

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the decentral.tv Sites and Service. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

decentral.tv also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that decentral.tv believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of decentral.tv, our Users or others. 

###  Your Choices 

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the decentral.tv Sites and Service, in which case decentral.tv may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the decentral.tv Sites and Service remain subject to our Terms of Service, even if you have deleted them from the pages associated with your account. If you inadvertently post materials in violation of our Term of Service, please contact decentral.tv using the feedback form. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact decentral.tv with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices by using the feedback form. 

###  Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites 

decentral.tv allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the decentral.tv Sites and Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the decentral.tv Sites and Service. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

decentral.tv does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks decentral.tv to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the decentral.tv Sites and Service, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

If you click on an advertisement, or click on a link that takes you to a website that is not operated by decentral.tv, you should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of that advertiser or website. decentral.tv's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. 

###  Our Commitment to Data Security 

decentral.tv uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to decentral.tv and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, decentral.tv makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If decentral.tv learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. decentral.tv may post a notice on the decentral.tv Sites and Service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using the feedback form. 

###  Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, decentral.tv does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the decentral.tv Sites and Service from persons under 14 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 14. If you are under 14 years of age, then please do not use or access the decentral.tv Sites at any time or in any manner. If decentral.tv learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 14 years of age has been collected on the decentral.tv Sites, then decentral.tv will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

###  Special Note to International Users 

The decentral.tv Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the decentral.tv Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the decentral.tv Sites, which are governed by U.S. and California law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Service, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

###  Changes and updates to this Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" at the top of this page. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the decentral.tv Sites and Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

###  Contact Information: 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please use our feedback form.
